# D E B J O H N S O N

PRODUCT DESIGNER

### SKILLS

UX/UI DESIGN

USER RESEARCH

**USER TESTING** 

PROTOTYPING

HTML/CSS

#### TOOLS

SKETCH

AFFINITY DESIGNER

INVISION

#### **ABOUT**

I'm a self-taught product designer and front-end developer (HTML/CSS). I was part of the founding team of a startup and wore many hats before discovering my passion for product design. My primary interests lie in user experience, user research, prototyping, and user testing.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Neon Labs**

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2013 - APRIL 2016

- Established company's design process and best practices
- Led user research to validate product directions;
   explored UX/UI concepts with rapid prototyping and user testing
- Designed analytics dashboard to display A/B testing data;
   worked with engineers to implement solution
- Designed internal tool to search through thousands of images generated by product

#### **Neon Labs**

DATA SCIENTIST

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2012 - FEB 2013

- Member of founding team; played crucial role in crafting early product vision
- Helped define company culture, vision, and values
- Worked closely with CEO to design pitch decks that helped raise over \$8M in venture funding

# **Carnegie Mellon University**

**RESEARCH ASSISTANT** 

PITTSBURGH, PA SEP. 2010 - FEB 2012

 Helped find commercial application for neuroscience research on how the brain perceives visual images, which led to the founding of Neon Labs

# **EDUCATION**

# **Dartmouth College**

B.A. Psychology, Music

HANOVER, NH 2006 - 2010

deb@debjohnson.design
debjohnson.design

603-738-0035